http://www.ccusa.com/privacyPolicy.aspx

×
Login or Apply
Choose the appropriate portal below to apply to a CCUSA program or login to your account.
FOOTPRINTS - Participant (all programs, except volunteer)
LOVE VOLUNTEERS - Participant (volunteer programs only)
Credits and Copyright Notice
This site was created by Camp Counselors USA (“CCUSA”). This entire site is copyright protected by CCUSA. All rights are reserved. CCUSA and its programs are registered United States trademarks and protected trademarks in other countries. You may not copy, reproduce, modify, distribute, transmit or post any part of this site without the written permission of CCUSA. You may, however, print pages of the site for your personal use.
Disclaimer
The materials on this site are provided for informational purposes only and are not guaranteed to be current, accurate or complete. This site is for your personal use only and may not be used for any commercial purpose.
Privacy Statement
CCUSA has created this privacy statement in furtherance of our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. This policy is effective as of Aug 1, 2005.
We reserve the right to change this statement at any time. Therefore, to view our latest privacy practices, please review this statement regularly. By using our site, you are deemed to have accepted the terms of this statement.
To help diagnose problems with our server, administer our site, gather broad demographic information and generate user statistics, we may collect information such as:
IP Address
Country of Origin
We will not share your information (including your email address) with any third party except (1) with your consent, (2) as required by law, or (3) to protect the rights, property or safety of CCUSA, including the prevention, detection, investigation or prosecution of attacks against our site or network.
This site contains links to other sites. CCUSA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such sites.
Types of Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you that either (1) you provide to us, or (2) we obtain with your authorization. Examples of such information include:
Name
Gender
Student status
Address
Phone Number
Email Address
Policy as to Disclosure of Information
For potential, current and former participants, we do not disclose to anyone other than our representatives and employees any nonpublic personal information obtained in the course of our business, except with your consent or as required by law or to protect the rights, property or safety of CCUSA. Be advised that it is possible that we could be compelled to disclose such information in response to the service upon us of a subpoena issued by a court or agency.
Protecting the Confidentiality and Security of Participant Information
We retain records relating to applicants and participants as part of our business. In order to assure the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with our professional standards.
Security
This site has electronic, physical and procedural security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
Cookies
CCUSA may set and access cookies on your computer. Cookies are small pieces of data set by your web browser and stored on your hard drive. CCUSA primarily uses cookies to remember your preferences, such as your home country, to help personalize your visits to our website and help facilitate navigation through the site. Cookies are non-essential and you can configure your browser to accept, reject or notify you when a cookie is set. You may, however, not be able to access all features of the CCUSA website if you have disabled your cookies.
Choice/Opt-Out
Please contact your local office if you wish to change your e-mail address or opt-out or receiving email messages. However, as stipulated in all CCUSA Program Agreements, CCUSA must be able to contact current, paid CCUSA participants via e-mail from the time of application until the completion of the program. Upon completion of the CCUSA program, former participants will be able to opt out of receiving further e-mails from CCUSA.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us via e-mail at feedback@ccusa.com.
Terms of Use
By accessing, using or viewing this website, you hereby agree to be bound by this Terms of Use Agreement (“Terms of Use”). CCUSA may revise these Terms of Use at any time by updating this posting. If you access, use or view this website after such revisions have been made, you will be bound by them. Therefore, you are advised to periodically review this page for such revisions. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, please exit this website.
THE INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE CCUSA WEBSITE IS FOR GENERAL INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES AND IS NOT INTENDED TO BE A COMPLETE DESCRIPTION OF THE TERMS, EXCLUSIONS, AND CONDITIONS APPLICABLE TO EVERY SERVICE OFFERED BY CCUSA. WHILE CCUSA AIMS TO KEEP THE INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE AS CURRENT AND ACCURATE AS POSSIBLE, THE CONTENT OF THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING ANY LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY CONTENT, IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. CCUSA ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN, OR RELIANCE UPON, THE INFORMATION IN THIS WEBSITE.
ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE OR PURPOSE, ARE HEREBY EXCLUDED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT OF THE LAW. CCUSA MAKES NO WARRANTY, AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY OBLIGATION, THAT THE CONTENT ON THIS WEBSITE WILL BE ACCURATE, COMPLETE, OR AVAILABLE AT ALL TIMES.
Limitations of Liability
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, CCUSA and our partners, associates, agents, attorneys, employees, subcontractors, assigns, successors, and affiliates SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, PERSONAL INJURY, MENTAL ANGUISH, OR EMOTIONAL DISTRESS THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE OR THE MATERIALS PROVIDED ON THIS WEBSITE. THIS INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES RESULTING FROM ACTIONS TAKEN BY YOU OR OTHERS IN RELIANCE ON INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS WEBSITE. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT CCUSA IS NOT LIABLE FOR ANY OFFENSIVE, DEFAMATORY, OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY VISITOR TO THIS WEBSITE, OR USER OF INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE. YOU AGREE THAT CCUSA SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES UNDER ANY INDEMNITY OR THEORY, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, TORT, PATENT OR COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT, OR OTHERWISE. SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY RESTRICT THESE LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY.
Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold CCUSA and our partners, associates, agents, attorneys, employees, subcontractors, assigns, successors, and affiliates harmless from and against any and all claims, demands, liabilities, judgments, losses, damages, costs, fees and expenses, including but not limited to reasonable attorneys’ fees arising from or relating to your use of this website or your acts or omissions relating to this website, including but not limited to: (1) infringement or misappropriation of any intellectual property rights, (2) defamation, libel, slander, obscenity, pornography, or violation of the rights of privacy or publicity, (3) spamming, or any other offensive, harassing or illegal conduct or violation of this Agreement, or (4) any damage or destruction to our website, or to us, or to another person which is caused by or otherwise results from your acts and omissions.
Termination for Failure to Comply with Terms of Use
We reserve the right to investigate suspected violations of these Terms of Use. If we become aware of possible violations, we may initiate an investigation that may include gathering information from you or any user involved and the complaining party, if any, and examination of other material. We may suspend the provision of our services temporarily, or we may permanently remove the material involved from our servers, cancel posts, provide warnings to you, or suspend or terminate your access to our services. We will determine what action will be taken in response to a violation on a case-by-case basis, and at our sole discretion.
You also hereby acknowledge that your breach of these Terms of Use may result in immediate and irreparable harm to CCUSA, for which there will be no adequate remedy at law, and that CCUSA shall be entitled to equitable relief to compel you to cease and desist all unauthorized use of this website. Your breach of these Terms of Use may also entitle CCUSA to bring an action against you for any and all other remedies available at law or in equity.
Applicable Laws
The laws of California govern this agreement. You agree that any legal action between you and CCUSA shall be brought exclusively in a federal or state court of competent jurisdiction sitting in California.
General Information
These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and CCUSA and govern your use of this website. This agreement supersedes any prior agreements between you and CCUSA. A waiver of any breach of any provision of these Terms of Use shall not be deemed to be a waiver of any repetition of such breach or in any manner affect any other terms or conditions of these Terms of Use. The failure of CCUSA to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of the Terms of Use is found to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of the Terms of Use remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of this website or the Terms of Use must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred.
Acknowledgement
You acknowledge that you have read and understand these Terms of Use, and that these Terms of Use have the same force and effect as a signed agreement.
